PHONE +84 948 935 300 EMAIL hi@auduongtuan.com WEBSITE/PORTFOLIO https://auduongtuan.com

INTRODUCTION

I'm a software designer and developer who strives to create good-experience digital products. Proudly having many skills that span a spectrum of disciplines, I use them to solve problems in creative, organized, and programmatic ways.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Despite having more experience in design, I'm looking for an engineer-driven role in which I could enhance my technical skills and dig into the product development process. Furthermore, it will be best if I can work in a position like <u>UX Engineer</u> - the dream job that makes use of my programming and design skills.

EXPERIENCE

BAEMIN Vietnam Oct 2022 - Current

Product designer / Front-end developer, Full-time

- Design Direct Discount feature for Merchant app.
- Conduct plan for new design system (web and mobile).
- Create design system's Figma web UI Kit and implement it based on MUI.
- Document design system's components in the Storybook site.
- Support FE developers in applying them to current products.
- Create <u>BM i18n</u> Internationalization Figma plugin to improve multi-language product development process (Figma API + React, Redux, TailwindCSS, Radix UI).

Aperia Vietnam Apr 2020 - Sep 2022

UI/UX designer / Front-end developer, Full-time

Worked as a designer (60%) and an associate front-end developer (40%) in the Design system team.

- Create and maintain UI kits in Sketch & Figma.
- Document components (UI specs, behaviors, and storybook) and design patterns.
- Prototype <u>complex concepts</u> using HTML/CSS/JS and implement some React components.
- Create Figma plugins to help improve design workflow.

Other works include:

- Implement and maintain <u>company website</u> (using WordPress and Tailwind CSS).
- Create some internal tools such as <u>Email Signature Generator</u>, <u>Sketch Cloud files</u> downloader.

Samsung Vietnam

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

UI/UX designer, Full-time

Joined a new Samsung design team in Vietnam to build apps for IOT devices.

ECOE Vietnam

Mar 2019 - Oct 2019

UI/UX designer, Contract

Joined a design team to build a new estate platform in Vietnam Market.

Viivue Web Boutique

Nov 2018 - Mar 2019

Web designer, Part-time

Worked as a part-time web designer for an agency (mainly using WordPress as a CMS).

Yeah1 Network

Dec 2017 - Jul 2018

Graphic designer and Video editor, Part-time

Worked as a part-time designer and video editor to create marketing materials, landing pages, and videos for Phở Đặc Biệt.

EDUCATION

University of Science (HCMUS)

BSc in Information Technology, class of 2021

University of Architecture HCMC (UAH)

BFA in Graphic Design, class of 2016

Keyframe Training

Motion graphic & C4D animation, class of 2016

Luong The Vinh High School For The Gifted

Specialization in Physics, class of 2013

SKILLS & STACK

Skills

- Product design
- Design system / DesignOps
- Web development
- Web standards, accessibility best practices
- · Motion graphics

Design Tools

- Figma, Sketch
- · Figma plugin development
- Adobe Creative Suite (PTS, AI, AE, Pr)
- Blender and C4D (basic experience)

Tech Stack

- HTML, CSS
- · Javascript, Typescript
- ReactJS, NextJS, jQuery
- Redux, Zustand
- SCSS, TailwindCSS, styled-components
- MUI, Ant Design, Radix UI, Headless UI
- PHP, WordPress
- React Native (basic experience)
- · Swift, Swift UI (basic experience)

LANGUAGES

- · Vietnamese (Native)
- English (IELTS 7.0)